noddus.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy | noddus

Privacy Policy

SNAPUPP TECHNOLOGIES SL., responsible for noddus.com, henceforth Noddus, makes this document available to all users in order to comply with the obligations laid down in Law 34/2002, of July 11, on Services of the Society of the Information and Electronic Commerce (LSSICE), BOE No. 166.

​

​Snapupp Technologies SL participates in the IAB Europe Transparency & Consent Framework and complies  with  its  Specifications  and  Policies.    
Snapupp Technologies’s  identification  number within the framework is 694.

Noddus is a content marketplace for advertisers, publishers and creators. Publishers use Noddus technology to monetize their ad spaces with campaigns served by Advertisers and agencies. Noddus technology collects and uses data to make online advertising more relevant as well as for reporting purposes.

Identification data:

  * Domain name: noddus.com

  * Commercial name: Noddus

  * Company name: SNAPUPP TECHNOLOGIES SL.

  * NIF: B87102760

  * Registered office: C / Clara Del Rey, 69, Bajo B, 28002, Madrid

  * e-mail: 

Since you'll be a user of our services, we want you to understand how we use the information and what you can do to protect your privacy. This privacy policy describes:​

  1. The methods we use to collect information.

  2. Which information we collect.

  3. What use we make of the information collected.

  4. Partners to whom we share the data.

  5. How we store the data.

  6. How to opt-out from Noddus personalized advertising

  7. Ways to access, update or delete your information.

1\. Methods used for user identification

Noddus does not collect or process any information that allows identifying a particular individual directly. Noddus uses 2 methods to single out users:

  * Cookie-based identification. Noddus drops a cookie on the user web and/or mobile browser. Cookies are used to single out a user and store a randomly generated identifier to identify their browser across visits.

  * Cookie-less environments. Noddus uses an alternate identification methodology based on IP address and user agent information.

We do not collect or process information related to name, home address, place of work, date of birth, email address, phone number or any other sensitive information.

2\. Type of information collected

With the information we collect we seek to offer an initial platform that matches as closely as possible to the needs of those who use it. In this case, we request personal information such as your name, email address, city where you live or your professional and/or social profiles.

We collect data through the tags our partners (publishers) embed in their sites. Data collected is as follows:

  * Interactions with Noddus ads (i.e. clicks, shares, etc.)

  * User Agent Information (i.e. browser type, OS, etc. )

  * Referring URL

  * Site URL

  * IP address

​Noddus performs the processing of personal data using third-party servers that may be located in different countries. We can carry out the processing of your personal data on a server that is not located in your country of residence.

3\. How we use the data collected

We use the information we collect to adjust the delivery of our advertising campaigns. The adjustments will be based on targeting (i.e. user location), frequency capping, analytics (i.e. to monitor the campaign performance), and programmatic ad delivery with our buyers and suppliers.

4\. How we share data with our partners

​We share aggregated non-personal information with our partners, including publishers and advertisers. For example, we may share information to show trends about the general use of our services and how campaigns perform.

​We will share your data with companies, organizations or individuals outside Noddus when we believe in good faith that there is a reasonable need for access to such data.

5\. How we keep the data in our systems

We keep the non-personal data up to 12 months from the date of collection.

6\. Opt-out from Noddus personalized Advertising

If you opt-out, you will still see ads although they may not be relevant to your interests. This action will only affect the browser you are using but will not opt you out on other devices or in other browsers you use. If cookies are cleared or deleted in your browser, this may delete the Noddus opt-out cookie, and you may need to renew your opt-out choice for that browser. You can opt-out from Noddus personalized advertising in your browser by clicking [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices).

If you want to disable Noddus personalized ad on your mobile device, please refer to your operating system settings. Please note that this is a device setting which will disable personalized ads from all providers, and not just for Noddus. Also, if your device’s advertising identifier is reset, you will need to renew your opt-out choice for that device.

7\. Update or disposal service

You will need to contact Noddus at this email address [info@noddus.com](mailto:info@noddus.com) if you need any modification of your data. In providing our services, we will protect your data by ensuring that it can’t be deleted accidentally or intentionally. If you need us to remove your information from our services, we may not immediately destroy residual copies stored on our active servers nor the data stored on our security systems.

​We may reject requests that jeopardise the privacy of other users or are not impractical.

​We will strive to provide ways to remove your data or update it quickly, unless we have to keep that information for legitimate business or legal reasons.
